[{"answer": "Hello", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 18, "question": "", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": "Hello.  May I speak with Maria Donaldson please", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 19, "question": "Hello", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Yes, hi, this is she", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 20, "question": "Hello.  May I speak with Maria Donaldson please", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Maria, hi.  This is Mark Lutz from the University of Georgia.  How are you today", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Yes, hi, this is she", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Hi, Dr. Lutz.  Im doing fine, thank you.  How are you", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Maria, hi.  This is Mark Lutz from the University of Georgia.  How are you today", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Just fine, thanks.  Please, call me Mark.  So are you ready for your interview t", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Hi, Dr. Lutz.  Im doing fine, thank you.  How are you", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Yes, Im ready", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Just fine, thanks.  Please, call me Mark.  So are you ready for your interview t", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " OK.  First of all, I want to start out by telling you a little bit about our office an", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Yes, Im ready", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": "OK", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 34, "question": " OK.  First of all, I want to start out by telling you a little bit about our office an", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Our department is called the Department of International Relations and we hav", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 35, "question": "OK", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Mmmhmmm", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Our department is called the Department of International Relations and we hav", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Right now, were looking to fill the position of academic advisor, which is a ver", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Mmmhmmm", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " I see.  How many of your students are undergrads", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Right now, were looking to fill the position of academic advisor, which is a ver", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Approximately 120", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 48, "question": " I see.  How many of your students are undergrads", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Wow!  Thats a lot", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Approximately 120", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Yes, it is.  Its a very challenging, but interesting and rewarding position", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Wow!  Thats a lot", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " It seems like it would be", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Yes, it is.  Its a very challenging, but interesting and rewarding position", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " So, with that said, Id like to start asking you some questions", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 52, "question": " It seems like it would be", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Sure, OK", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 53, "question": " So, with that said, Id like to start asking you some questions", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Can you tell me what are your greatest strengths", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Sure, OK", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Yes.   Id say my strengths are my communication and organizational skills.  M", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Can you tell me what are your greatest strengths", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " OK, good.  How about your weaknesses?  What are those", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Yes.   Id say my strengths are my communication and organizational skills.  M", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Well, I dont really have any weaknesses that would affect my ability to perfor", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 63, "question": " OK, good.  How about your weaknesses?  What are those", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " OK.  How do you handle stress", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Well, I dont really have any weaknesses that would affect my ability to perfor", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " If I feel stressed at work, I try to take a break for a few minutes.  Do somethin", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 70, "question": " OK.  How do you handle stress", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Very good.  What about multi-tasking?  Are you comfortable with this", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 74, "question": " If I feel stressed at work, I try to take a break for a few minutes.  Do somethin", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Oh, yes.  Multi-tasking was something I had to do everyday in my previou", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Very good.  What about multi-tasking?  Are you comfortable with this", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Thats good to hear.  This is our last question today  why do you want thi", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Oh, yes.  Multi-tasking was something I had to do everyday in my previou", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " I feel that my skills and experience are a great match for the position.  I coul", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Thats good to hear.  This is our last question today  why do you want thi", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Now, do you have any questions for me", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 89, "question": " I feel that my skills and experience are a great match for the position.  I coul", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Yes.  What is the next step in the hiring process", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Now, do you have any questions for me", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Well, today we are interviewing 6 candidates by phone.  After this, we will b", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Yes.  What is the next step in the hiring process", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " OK, thank you", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Well, today we are interviewing 6 candidates by phone.  After this, we will b", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  Its been a pleasure talking with you today.  Well be in touc", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 97, "question": " OK, thank you", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " Thank you very much for the opportunity to interview for the position", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 101, "question": " Youre welcome.  Its been a pleasure talking with you today.  Well be in touc", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": "Bye now", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 102, "question": " Thank you very much for the opportunity to interview for the position", "qSentId": 101},{"answer": " Bye-bye", "docId": "01-02", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Bye now", "qSentId": 102}]
